http://www.mussellcrane.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust. Accordingly we maintain the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online. Any information you give to us will be held with extreme care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to.
If you choose to email us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, we will not use the information for any purpose other than to respond to your inquiry. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease any personal information collected on our site. Our web site logs are not personally identifiable and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site.
Our web sites track information about the visits to the web site. For example, it compiles statistics that show the daily number of visitors to the site, the daily requests received for particular files on the web site, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used internally to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.
On our web site, you may find links to third party web sites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy policies or content on third party sites. Therefore, it is recommended that you read the privacy policy of third party web sites for your information.If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please don't hesitate to contact us.
Home
Cranes
Runway & Columns
Overhead Cranes
Box Girder Cranes
Jibs & Davits
Gantry Cranes
Trailer Reloads
Terms | Privacy | © 2020 Mussell Crane Mfg., All rights reserved | Website by Pixelgems
